//creating an array and passing the number,question , options ,and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite anime",
        answer: "one piece",
        Options: [
            "one piece",
            "naruto",
            "attack on titans",
            "death note",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite color",
        answer: "black",
        Options: [
            "white",
            "grey",
            "black",
            "blue",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite hobby",
        answer: "playing guitar",
        Options: [
            "gym",
            "watching series/animes",
            "coding",
            "playing guitar",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite platform",
        answer: "instagram",
        Options: [
            "tiktok",
            "facebook",
            "instagram",
            "youtube",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite serie",
        answer: "the walking dead",
        Options: [
            "game of thrones",
            "the walking dead",
            "dark",
            "lost",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite serie",
        answer: "the walking dead",
        Options: [
            "game of thrones",
            "the walking dead",
            "dark",
            "lost",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite superhero",
        answer: "spiderman",
        Options: [
            "Ironman",
            "spiderman",
            "batman",
            "doctor strange",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite film",
        answer: "interstellar",
        Options: [
            "interstellar",
            "forgotten",
            "inception",
            "the invisible guest",
        ]

    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite time to study ki yebde maghsour 9bal exmanet",
        answer: "5 taa sba7",
        Options: [
            "5 taa sba7",
            "10 taa sba7 ",
            "5 taa laachiya",
            "10 taa lil",
        ]

    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite food",
        answer: "kosksi b lben",
        Options: [
            "Ma9rouna",
            "kosksi b lben",
            "3de batata bel maadnous w lbsal",
            "lasania",
        ]

    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite fruit",
        answer: "Moz",
        Options: [
            "3neb",
            "Dele3",
            "tefe7",
            "Moz",
        ]

    },

    {
        numb: 11,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite place to go",
        answer: "cinéma",
        Options: [
            "cinéma",
            "b7ar",
            "restaurant",
            "9ahwa",
        ]

    },

    {
        numb: 12,
        question:"what is ahmed favourite season ",
        answer: "winter",
        Options: [
            "summer",
            "spring",
            "winter",
            "autumn",
        ]

    },


];